

# CLARK JAMES EVANGELISTA

**PROGRAMMER** 

### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

Experienced Technician with a demonstrated history of working in the electrical and electronic manufacturing industry. Skilled in Network Administration with a very strong Programming background and has a newly completed MERN Stack Course from McLaren College.

### **LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS**

Microsoft Technology Associate:
Networking Fundamentals
(MTA) - Microsoft
E755-2920

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures - freeCodeCamp



Ibaraki, Japan



+818091660229



cjamesevangelista@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/clark-james-evangelista-34ab2a184

# **EDUCATION**

McLaren College MERN Stack Course | 2021 - 2021

MongoDB - document database Express(.js) - Node.js web framework

React(.js) - a client-side JavaScript framework Node(.js) - the premier JavaScript web server

\_\_\_\_\_

Bulacan State University
Bachelor's degree, Information Technology | 2012 - 2016

# **EXPERIENCE**

Technician Flex | Mar 2019 - Dec 2020

Food Manufacturing - Monteur Tsukuba Bando, Ibaraki | Apr 2017 - Feb 2019

Food Manufacturing - Table Mark Iwai, Ibaraki | Aug 2016 - Mar 2017

#### **SKILLS AND EXPERTISE**

